Guide to the Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records, 1982-1993.
Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records
- Miscellaneous unsorted materials, Date unknown (Box 29)
- US Bases Articles 1988, 1988 (Box 30)
- CALL Nuclear Free Philippines Coalition, Date unknown (Box 30)
- US Bases Clippings 1988, 1988 (Box 30)
- Pre-1988 Bases Articles, 1988 (Box 30)
- Department of Defense Documents, Date unknown (Box 30)
- RP Senate, 1991 (Box 30)
- NFPC Statements: Church Partners-Statements/Correspondence, 1991 (Box 30)
- US Congress Bills, Hearings etc, 1991 (Box 30)
- CCHRP Press Releases/Statements, 1991 (Box 30)
- RP Press, 1991 (Box 30)
- US Press, 1991 (Box 30)
- FFP: Impact on 92 Elections (bribes, etc), 1991 (Box 30)
- FFP: Draft of Treaty 4/91, 1991-04 (Box 30)
- Bases (misc) 1991, 1991 (Box 30)
- Background Info/Correspondence, Date unknown (Box 30)
- - US Military Bases in the Philippines: a briefing packet, Date unknown (Box 30)
- US Bases clippings 1991, 1991 (Box 30)
- "Crossroads" 1991, 1991 (Box 30)
- US Bases Dept of Defense: Documents 1990, 1990 (Box 30)
- US Bases Statements 1990, 1990 (Box 30)
- Continuing US Interference: Obstacle to Sovereignty and Peace in the Philippines and the third World (publication), Date unknown (Box 30)
- US Bases and Environmental Destruction 1990, 1990 (Box 30)
- US Church Resolutions re Bases 1990, 1990 (Box 30)
- Bases Negotiations 1990, 1990 (Box 30)
- Key Clippings 1990, 1990 (Box 30)
- US Bases Clippings: 1990, 1990 (Box 30)
- US Bases articles 1990, 1990 (Box 30)
- US Bases Clippings 1989, 1989 (Box 30)
- US Church Resolutions re Bases 1988-1989, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
- Consultations on US Bases February 4, 1989, 1989-02-04 (Box 30)
- Articles/information, 1989 (Box 30)
- Hospitality Industry 1989, 1989 (Box 30)
- Resource packet on US Bases 1989, 1989 (Box 30)
- Key Clippings 1989, 1989 (Box 30)
- Petitions against military bases, Date unknown (Box 30)
- Summary of proceedings of AMRSP-CONTAK-NCCP-CCHRP Consultation, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Reports, 1983-1992 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- National Political issues; Reaffirming the Philippine left, 1983-1994 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Church Trends, no. 1; What does the Lord require of us, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Behind the Mask, Human Rights Resources Office for Latin America, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Walking in harmony; Nuclear-Free Pacific Conference-1980, 1973-1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- The Philippines: American corporations, martial law and underdevelopment, 1973-1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- In solidarity for full humanity, 1973-1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Laya: feminist quarterly, 1973-1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- The future of the missionary enterprise, 1973-1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- The legacy of colonialism helath care in Southeast Asia, 1973-1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Report of the Asian Human Rights Commission Study, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Mission to the Philippines, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Philippine human rights update, vols. 3,4, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Kalinangan, vol. 8, no. 2, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Maps; Posters, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Debate: Philippine left review, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Rebolusyon, Central Committee, Communist Party of the Philippines, special issue, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Stand for socialism against modern revisionism, Armando Liwanag, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Various papers, 1980-1991 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Various papers, 1983-1992 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Tugon: an ecumenical journal, 1985-1991 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Poems, 1973-1991 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Various papers, 1979-1988 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- CCHRP Future -- 1988, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Phils 11/11/88, 1988-11-11 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Amnesty International Philippines Report 1988, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, 1988-09-26 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, 1988-09-26 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- CCHRP Personnel Committee meeting, January 15, 1988. Includes agenda, 1988-01-15 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Minutes of Steering Committee meeting, January 21, 1988; CCHRP memo for urgent action, 1988-01-21 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Ruth Harris: various publications, newsletters, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- CCHRP Steering Committee minutes of meeting, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Budget for 1988-1989, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Requests for project funding and various publications, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- CCHRP Personnel Committee meeting, May 3, 1988, 1988-05-03 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- CCHRP Steering Committee Meeting, March 1, 1988, 1988-03-01 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  Includes consultation on US policy toward the Phils and statements on the withdrawl of US military bases from the Phils
- CCHRP Steering Committee Meeting, May 3, 1988, 1988-05-03 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Dante Simbulan's Party, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- 1988 CCHRP: Contak and Epic, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Minutes of the CCHRP Steering Committee Meeting, January 21-23, 1988, 1988-01-21-1988-12-04 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  Includes a December 4, 1988 minutes of meeting
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, San Francisco, November 13-15, 1987, 1987-11-13-1987-11-15 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- CCHRP-February 20, 1987, 1987-02-20 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- CCHRP Steering Committee Meeting, June 18, 1987, 1987-06-18 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- CCHRP Steering Committee Meeting Minutes 1987, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Mission Study Book on Philippines 1987, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Nightmare at Menidola Bridge; CCHRP Urgent Action, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Philippines: Mendiola Bridge Incident, January 1987, 1987-01 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Ruth Harris, 1986-1987. Includes handwritten notes, newsclippings and publications, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Maryknoll Missioners re Alsa Masa in Mindanao, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, newsletters, minutes of meetings, newsclippings on the political and human rights situation in the Aquino Administration, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Lean Alejandro, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Report of a US-Philippine Fact-finding Mission to the Philippines, May 20-30 headed by Ramsey Clark, 1987-05-20-1987-05-30 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Philippine Conference for Human Rights, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Institute on Religion and Democracy (IRD)/Philippines, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Key mailing list - Philippine Witness, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Emergency Strategy meeting on Sri-Lanka, May 28, 1986, 1986-05-28 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Ruth Harris, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  Includes handwritten notes, correspondence, newsletters, publications
- 1986 CCHRP Statements on the Philippines, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- WCC Book - Human rights violations in the Philippines. Press Conf. 2/6/1986, 1986-02-06 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- CCHRP/MIP Briefing 1/15/85, 1985-01-15 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  Report on the work of the Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines 1984
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, Columbus, Ohio, 1985, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Tom Obrien, Maryknoll Missioners, Davao City, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Newsclippings from New York Times, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Disarmament/Nuclear (Some Implications of Chernobyl by Dr. Seymour Melman), 1986 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- WCC/Church and Society Newsletter #4 June 1986 re Manila Consultation on Technology, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 40)
- CCHRP Steering Committee (Meeting) 5/14/86 12:00-4:30 Room 1529, 1986-05-14 (Box 32, Folder 41)
- CCHRP and US church leaders re Statement on human rights in the Philippines, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Newsletters, periodical articles, newsclippings on the Philippines, 1983-1986 (Box 32, Folder 43)
- Articles, press briefing re human rights violations in the Philippines, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 44)
- Letter/invitation of Ramsey Clark re reception for Bobby Ortaliz, KMU Vice-Chair, October 16, 1985, 1985-10-16 (Box 32, Folder 45)
- Press Conference, Fr. Luis Hechanova, October 7, 1985, 1985-10-07 (Box 32, Folder 46)
- Newsclippings, newsletters on the Philippines snap election, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 47)
- CCA News - The name is justice, process, solidarity, October 1985, 1985-10 (Box 32, Folder 48)
- National Catholic News Service, April 10, 1986, 1986-04-10 (Box 32, Folder 49)
- Columban Fathers Justice and Peace Office statement on the crisis in the Philippines, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 50)
- CCHRP Annual Meeting, December 8, 1984. Includes agenda, budget, conference statements, 1984-12-08 (Box 32, Folder 51)
- Philippine debt to foreign banks, by John E. Lind, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 52)
- Meeting (Task Force) on Finances, CCHRP, January 10, 1983, 1983-01-10 (Box 32, Folder 53)
- Joint Philippine-Korea-USCMA meeting on joint work, 1984-06-18 (Box 32, Folder 54)
- Draft of proposal to USCMA Board, 1984-06-18 (Box 32, Folder 54)
- Minutes of meeting, CCHRP, September 18, 1984, 1984-06-18 (Box 32, Folder 54)
- Philippines: information packet, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 55)
- Amicus brief: Crockett vs. Reagan, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 56)
- Executive Order on Intelligence gathering, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 57)
- WSCF Asia re Arrests of Philippine SCMers and KSCF Gen Sec, Ahn Jaewoong, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 58)
- Churches Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines, 1979, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 59)
- Philippines, 1979-1980. Includes correspondence, newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 60)
- Report of an Amnesty International Mission to the Republic of the Philippines, 11-28 November 1981, 1981-11-11-1981-11-28 (Box 32, Folder 61)
- Asia Pacific Center, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Papers of 10th Annual National Ecumenical Conference in the Philippines, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  Philippines in the Asia/Pacific Context: Challenges for US Solidarity Work, Columbus, Ohio
- Asia Pacific Center meeting, December 4, 7, 1994, 1994-12-04-1994-12-07 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, November 18, 1994, 1994-11-18 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, Summer 1994, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- CCHRP/PJAG Joint Meeting, May 25, 1994, 1994-05-25 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- CCHRP - Key documents, 1990-1992 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  Includes a list of CCHRP publications
- CCHRP addresses/stationary, 1992-04-01 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  Lists addresses of Steering Committee members and participants to the CCHRP-NCCP-AMRSP-CONTAK Consultation in Manila and Tagaytay City, April 1, 1992
- CCHRP Officers meeting, January 11, 1993, 1993-01-11 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- National Council of Churches USA Policy Statement on US-Philippine relations (drafts), 1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- National Council of Churches/Philippine Joint Action Group, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- CCHRP Steering Committee and Officers - May 1993, 1993-05 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  Includes minutes of meeting; correspondence; reports; newsletters
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1993 - Speeches, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Papers of the 8th Annual National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, Cambridge, Massachusetts, November 13-15, 1992, 1992-11-13-1992-11-15 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- CCHRP Officers Meeting, September 15, 1993, 1993-09-15 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- CCHRP Steering Committee and Officers meetings, May 25, 26, 1993, 1993-05-25-1993-05-26 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- CCHRP Officers meetings, August 1993, 1993-08 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- CCHRP plans, Summer 1993, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- CCHRP Steering Committee and Officers meetings, January 1993, 1993-01 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- CCHRP By-laws, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- CCHRP Key contacts, 1991-1996 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Papers of the 9th Annual National Ecumenical Conference in the Philippines, Seattle, Washington, November 5-7, 1993, 1993-11-05-1993-11-07 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Philippine development forum issues, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Papers of the CCHRP-NCCP-AMRSP-CONTAK Consultation, Tagaytay City, March 30-April 1, 1992, 1992-03-30-1992-04-01 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- March for life - Mariceles, Bataan to Capas Tarlac, April 5-11, 1992, 1992-04-05-1992-04-11 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- CCHRP May 11-12 meetings and CCHRP-NCCP-AMRSP-CONTAK Consultation papers, 1992-05-11-1992-05-12 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Summary of Consultation income and expenses, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- PJAG-CCHRP meeting, May 1992, 1992-05 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines Campaign Coordinating Committee, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meetings, October 1992, 1992-10 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- CCHRP relationships, 1990-1992 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  Includes correspondence, project proposals, newsletters and publications
- NCCP International Peach Conference Planning, Toronto, Canada, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, September 8, 1992, 1992-09-08 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, July 13, 1992, 1992-07-13 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- CCHRP finances, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- CCHRP Program Officers and Steering Committee meetings, May 11-12, 1992, 1992-05-11-1992-05-12 (Box 33, Folder 36)
- CCHRP - April 11, 1992, 1992-04-11 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- Minutes of CCHRP Steering Committee meetings, January 1992, 1992-01 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  Includes agenda and list of officers and committees
- CCHRP Steering Committee meetings, January 1992, 1992-01 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- CCHRP letter to Pres. Ramos and Manuel Romero, Chair, National Democratic Front, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, 1991 Campaign, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  "Beating Swords into Plowshares: toward a sustainable peace"
- Philippine materials, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  Includes reports, newsletters, etc. on human rights, Moro people, 1992 Philippine election, etc
- CCHRP Steering Committee Retreat, June 1-3, 1991, 1991-06-01-1991-06-03 (Box 33, Folder 43)
- Papers of the 7th Annual National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, 1991-10-25-1991-10-27 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  "Sustainable Peace: a New World Order," Ann Arbor, Michigan
- CCHRP - Military Bases, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 45)
- CCHRP - Lobbying (re US-Philippines relations, military bases), April 13-16, 1991, 1991-04-13-1991-04-16 (Box 33, Folder 46)
- Papers of the 6th National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippine, 1990-11-16-1990-11-18 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  "Beating Swords into Plowshares: Towards a Sustainable Peace," Pasadena, CA
- CCHRP - Consultation/Lobby Day, March 11-13, 1990, 1990-03-11-1990-03-13 (Box 33, Folder 48)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting minutes, December 19, 1989, 1989-12-19 (Box 33, Folder 49)
- CCHRP - Officers and Staff meeting, February 8, 1990, 1990-02-08 (Box 33, Folder 50)
- CCHRP-related organizations, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 51)
- US-Philippine Relations in Transition, 1990-03-12-1990-03-13 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  A Consultation on US Policy Toward the Philippines and Philippine Lobby Day, Washington, DC
- CCHRP - Office, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 53)
- CCHRP Officers and Committee members, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 54)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, December 19, 1989, 1989-12-19 (Box 33, Folder 55)
- CCHRP Steering Committee, 1989, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 56)
- United Church of Christ statements re killing of UCCP members in Devao del Sur, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 57)
- CCHRP future directions, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 58)
- NCCC Philippine Joint Action Group, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 59)
- Letter re activities of the CCHRP, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 60)
- Brochures on NCCC Ecumenical Travel Seminar to the Philippines. Also includes announcements for Korea and South Africa, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 61)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting minutes, December 19, 1989, 1989-12-19 (Box 33, Folder 62)
- National Ecumenical Conference of the Philippines 1989 Campaign (with the Theme: Militarization), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 63)
- Philippine-related organizations, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 64)
- Philippine Witness issue #23 and Mailing list, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 65)
- Papers of the 1989 National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, Philadelphia, PA, November 10-12, 1989, 1989-11-10-1989-11-12 (Box 33, Folder 66)
- Newclippings, publications on Philippine insurgency/counterinsurgency and human rights, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 67)
- Exposure Tour to the Philippines, March 1-16, 1986, 1986-03-01-1986-03-16 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Christianity and Crisis articles, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- CCHRP Press briefing and Steering Committee meeting, April 4, 1986, 1986-04-04 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- CCHRP Personnel, October 1983, 1983-10 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meetings, January 1986, 1986-01 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, September 8, 1986, 1986-09-08 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- CCHRP - Harris - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- CCHRP Study/Reflection/Planning/URM meeting, July 1-2, 1986 Alma Mathew/Cont., 1986-07-01-1986-07-02 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Philippine resources, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  Includes Philippine Witness issues and articles on the newly installed Aquino government
- Church Office for Justice in Asia (COJA), 1986 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Church Office for Justice in Asia re Philippines - Organizational meeting, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting minutes, April 2, 1986, 1986-04-02 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- US ultra-right in the Philippines, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting minutes, March 26, 1985, 1985-03-26 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, July 25, 1985, 1985-07-25 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Letters of Doug Cunningham to the editors of Christianity and Crisis reacting to an article, "Davao, Mindanao", 1985 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  Includes essays accounting his experiences as a member of a fact-finding mission in northern Mindanao
- NCCC Philippine Joint Action Group, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Philippines-CCHRP Exposure Trip - 1985, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- NCC-PJAG, December 3, 1985; NCCUSA-CCHRP Strategy Consultation on the New Situation in the Philippines, November 26, 1985, 1985-11-26 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- CCHRP Budget, 1985, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Conference Proceedings of the National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, 1985-11-22-1985-11-23 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  "Building Solidarity with the Filipino People," Columbus, Ohio
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, May 10, 1985, 1985-05-10 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- CCHRP: Urgent Action, 1985, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Philippines: information packet for the National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, Columbus, Ohio, November 22-23, 1985, 1985-11-22-1985-11-23 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, March 26, 1985, 1985-03-26 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, February 15, 1985, 1985-02-15 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Correspondence from the General Board of Global Ministries, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- re CCHRP Publications, Philippine Witness and CCHRP Newsletter, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- CCHRP National Lobby Day, Washington, DC, May 2, 1985, 1985-05-02 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Joint NCC-CCHRP Strategy Session on the New Situation in the Philippines, 1985-11-22-1985-11-23 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, Columbus, Ohio, November 22-23, 1985, 1985-11-22-1985-11-23 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Philippines: CCHRP Health and Medical Campaign, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- General information: Toward a Common Sharing of Technology: an international workshop, Manila, July 19-August 2, 1986, 1986-07-19-1986-08-02 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- The Philippines: the Philippines Government Response to the Report of an AI Mission … 11-28 November 1981 and AI's Reply to the Government's Response, 1981-11-11-1981-11-28 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- CCHRP Luncheon with Sen. Jose W. Diokno as guest, September 18, 1984, 1984-09-18 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- CCHRP Annual Meeting, December 8, 1985, 1985-12-08 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Bishop Labayen meeting, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- CCHRP Solidarity Event, September 18, 1984, 1984-09-18 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, March 8, 1984, 1984-03-08 (Box 34, Folder 38)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, January 9, 1984, 1984-01-09 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  Includes the CCHRP 1984 Working Budget with Projected budget for 1985
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, October 18, 1984, 1984-10-18 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Karl Gaspar's Letters, 1984, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Correspondence with Patty Wagner, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 42)
- CCHRP Education Committee meeting, February 2, 1984, 1984-01-09-1984-02-02 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- Minutes of CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, January 9, 1984, 1984-01-09-1984-02-02 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- CCHRP Luncheon meeting with Sen. Diokno, September 18, 1984, 1984-09-18 (Box 34, Folder 44)
- Correspondence with Ecumenical Movement for Justice and Peace (Philippines), 1984 (Box 34, Folder 45)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, April 25, 1984, 1984-04-25 (Box 34, Folder 46)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, July 18, 1984, 1984-07-18 (Box 34, Folder 47)
- CCHRP - Advent Campaign, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 48)
- Papers of the National Conference on the May 14 Elections in the Philippines, NYC, April 15, 1984, 1984-04-15 (Box 34, Folder 49)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting minutes, February 2, 1984, 1984-02-02 (Box 34, Folder 50)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting minutes, June 13, September 9, 1983, 1983-06-13-1983-09-09 (Box 34, Folder 51)
- International Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines meeting of some key people of the US Host Committee, October 18, 1983, 1983-06-13-1983-09-09 (Box 34, Folder 51)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, January 6, 1983. Includes a mailing list, 1983-01-06 (Box 34, Folder 52)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, September 9, 1983, 1983-09-09 (Box 34, Folder 53)
- CCHRP Steering Committee meeting, October 21, 1983, 1983-10-21 (Box 34, Folder 54)
- Joint Dinner: CCHRP and NACHRIK, December 9, 1983, 1983-12-09 (Box 34, Folder 55)
- CCHRP - Ruth Harris, 1982-1983, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  Includes minutes of meetings, summary of receipts and disbursements, working budget, newspaper clippings
- Philippines resources, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  Includes newspaper clippines, publications
- CCHRP Subcommittee on Personnel Review, 1979-1984 (Box 34, Folder 58)
- CCHRP Restructure papers, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  Includes By-laws, minutes of meetings
- CCHRP Annual Membership meeting, December 10, 1983, 1983-12-10 (Box 34, Folder 60)
- Memorandum to PJAG re CCHRP's participation in the campaign against the US military intervention in the Philippines, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 61)
- Philippine resources, 1982-1987 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  Includes newspaper clippings, publications
- Philippine resources, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 63)
- Research: Sobrepena/Kennedy, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  The impact of private and voluntary aid projects on the self-reliance and empowerment of people in the Philippines
- Papers of the Forum on Philippine Alternatives International Conference, San Francisco, April 3-5, 1993, 1993-04-03-1993-04-05 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Peace - includes newsletters, statements, publications, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Contains publications, newsletters on church and liberation theology, 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Ultra-right in the Philippines, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Women, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Information on the film: The Global Assembly Line, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- CCHRP Film, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  Contains documents pertaining to a docu-drama TV film project to address critical issues related to the Philippines
- Papers of the International Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, Nyack, New York, September 27-October 2, 1983, 1983-09-27-1983-10-02 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- International Conference of Philippine Support Groups, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 9)